Oliver Inglis

Q 202 Sketch Apartments, 42 Whitehorse Lane, E1 3FY London, United Kingdom

+44 7708 096992

▼ we.tl/t-JT4rHQRXCB

✓ ollie@theinglistwins.com

in linkedin.com/in/oliver-inglis

github.com/oginglis

Profile

I launched my own company in 2015 and have 5+ years of experience delivering multimedia projects to high-profile clients including Diageo, Royal Dutch Shell and Major League Baseball. As company director, I have gained firsthand experience of developing a marketing strategy, negotiating contracts, managing budgets and delivering high quality products to tight deadlines.

Professional Experience

Jul 2015 – present London, United Kingdom TWIN LDN, Creative Director & Founder

- Launched TWIN LDN, a creative agency specialising in video, animation and graphic design. We also support clients to develop advertising materials and branding.
- Clients include: Red Bull, Diageo, Royal Dutch Shell, Major League Baseball, Smirnoff, Tanqueray, Mitchell & Ness, Captain Morgan and Eventbrite.
- Delivered graphic design and layout for an environmental proposal that secured 1 million GBP for a major philanthropic organisation.

Aug 2016 – Aug 2018 London, United Kingdom NVS Music Group, Editor & Videographer

- Produced high-impact videos and promotional content for three annual international music festivals: Sunfall, Outlook and Dimensions, raising their profile to achieve sell-out attendance.
- Led a six-person team to make a 16-part documentary series filmed in Europe.
- Collaborated with David Rodigan, the internationally acclaimed reggae DJ and broadcaster, to produce a documentary that has been viewed over 158 000 times.

Technical Skills

Premiere Pro, After Effects, Photoshop, Cinema 4D, Illustrator, Javascript, Ruby on Rails, Github, Git, CSS, Web Development, HTML, SQL, React, Redux

Projects

Full portfolio available at www.twinldn.dev

Icarebnb, Ruby On Rails, Javascript - (http://www.icarebnb.org/)

- Designed, implemented and shipped to production a Rails prototype app to help charities source temporary accommodation for vulnerable clients.
- Two refugee support organisations have expressed an interest in the finished product.
- Features include: integrated geocoder API, Pusher JavaScript live-chat and Algolia powered search-bar.

Swipe Chef, Ruby on Rails, JavaScript, API's, Scraping (http://www.swipechef.com/)

- Collaborated with four other developers to create a Rails prototype app with a Tinder-style interface to enable users to filter their culinary preferences and swipe to find recipes to cook.
- Features include: swipeable JavaScript interface and web-scraping.

Education

Oct 2019 – Dec 2019
London, United Kingdom
London, United Kingdom

Sep 2016 – Jul 2019
Le Wagon (N°1 Coding Bootcamp on Switchup 2020),

Full-Stack Developer Program (Batch #319)
9-week intensive coding bootcamp learning Ruby, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES6, SQL, git, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on Rails.

University Of Leeds, English and Film Studies BA

Awarded 2:1